Holding Our Own; Records apap365
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Women's Music and Video, 1986; Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Women's Resources Distribution Company, 1982-1985 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Women's Studies, 1985; Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Women's Studies SUNYA, 1983; 1987 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Women's Studio Workshop, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Women's Video Collective, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Young Woman Award, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
- YWCA: Families in Violence Project, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 7)